-Phoebe,could you get that,please? -Why?
菲比，可以麻煩接個電話嗎？ 為什麼？
Just because you're too lazy to get up off your tushy?
就因為你懶得動？
No,it's just that all the people in the world I would want to talk to are right here.
不是，只是因為在全世界 我只想跟你說話
好吧
Sucker.
真好騙
Hello?
喂？
-Hey,Joey! -Hey,Phoebe.
喬伊 菲比
I need a favor.
幫我個忙好嗎？
I forgot the PlN to my ATM card. Can you get it for me?
我忘記提款卡的密碼 你可以幫我去找嗎？
Sure. Where is it?
好啊，在哪裡？
I scratched it on the ATM machine on the corner.
我刻在提款機的角落那裡
So you're 5-6-3-9?
原來5639是你的密碼
That's it! Thanks.
沒錯，菲比，謝了
-Wanna talk to Chandler? -Let me talk to him.
你要跟錢德說話嗎？ 是喬伊嗎？讓我跟他說
He didn't believe in my movie...
不要！他不相信我的電影
...which is a big mistake, because it is real. Real.
他大錯特錯 這次的電影是真的！…
Tribbiani,get back to work. Break time's over.
崔比亞尼 快回去工作，休息時間結束了
-Who was that? -My stunt double. Yeah.
剛才那個是誰？ 我的替身
He's getting a little too familiar for my tastes.
他有點太沒大沒小了
I've tried to apologize.
我這星期來都試著跟他道歉
If I can't do it on the phone, I'll go and do it in person.
若他不讓我在電話上說 我就直接殺過去當面說
I heard that. Can you put him on?
菲比，我聽到了，請他聽電話
好
Don't come out here.
你別過來
I support you 100% and I wanna prove that to you in person.
不行…我百分之百支持你 我要當面證明給你看
I got that. I forgive you. Don't come out here.
收到，我原諒你，你別過來
You haven't taken my calls for a week.
原諒我？ 你一星期都不接我電話
I'm totally over it. Friends forever. Don't come out here.
錢德，我早都不介意了 咱們是一輩子的朋友 你別過來
Would you mind doing a picture with us?
可以跟我們照張相嗎？
-What was that? -Entertainment Tonight.
那是什麼？ 「今夜娛樂」節目
Good talking to you and don't come out here.
好了，很高興跟你說話 你別過來
The One in Vegas
本集播出：「賭城行」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Monica? I'm sorry I'm late.
摩妮卡，抱歉我遲到了
摩妮卡？
菲比？
I'm so sorry. Have you been here long?
菲比，真對不起 你到很久了嗎？
That's okay.
沒關係啦
What the hell took you so long?
你怎麼拖了那麼久？
You can't tell Chandler. I ran into Richard.
好，不許你跟錢德說 我遇見了理查
-Which Richard? -The Richard.
哪個理查？ 那個理查
Richard Simmons? Oh,my God!
理查西蒙斯?（減重專家） 天啊
No,my ex-boyfriend Richard. You know, the tall guy, mustache.
不是啦，是我前男友理查 個子高高，有鬍子那個
Okay, that actually makes more sense. How was it?
好吧，這就說得過去了 情況如何？
It was really nice. We talked and I had lunch with him.
好極了，我們先是閒聊 後來一起吃了個午飯
That's weird. I dreamed you had lunch with Richard.
怪了，我有夢到你跟理查吃飯
-Really? -Again, Richard Simmons.
真的？ 不過是跟理查西蒙斯啦
Go on.
你繼續說
The strange part was he was really nice...
奇怪的是雖然他很棒也很帥
...and he looks great, but I didn't feel anything.
但是我對他完全沒感覺了
So why can't we tell Chandler?
那為什麼不能跟錢德說？
It'll freak him out and tomorrow's our anniversary. I don't wanna spoil it.
因為他聽了一定會發神經 明天就是我們的紀念日 我不想搞砸
I can't believe you guys have lasted a whole year!
不敢相信你們交往一年了
Wow, I owe Rachel 20 bucks.
我欠瑞秋20美元
On a totally different bet.
那是完全不相干的賭局啦
-It's almost our anniversary! -I know.
一週年紀念日快到了 我知道
One year ago today,I was just your annoying friend Chandler.
你相信嗎？一年前的今天 我還是只是煩人的朋友錢德
Now you're just my annoying friend Chandler.
現在你是我煩人的朋友錢德
I got you a gift.
我幫你買了禮物
-It's not till tomorrow. -I know,but you have to open it today.
紀念日明天才到 我知道，但你今天就要開禮物
Okay! There you go!
我來啦
It's two tickets to Vegas!
兩張去賭城的機票
Yeah! For this weekend! It'll be perfect.
這週末的來回機票 一定很完美
You'll see Joey, plus,we'll start our celebration on the plane.
不但能去看喬伊 還能在飛機上開始過紀念日
We can call it our "Plane-aversary."
就叫做「飛機紀念日」吧
Do we have to?
一定要這樣叫？
This is great, but Joey didn't want any of us there.
這是很棒沒錯 但喬伊說了不要我們過去
He doesn't want us to go to any trouble. He'll be excited when we surprise him.
他只是怕麻煩我們而已 到時我們突然出現 他一定超興奮的
Plus,we get to have our own "Anna-Vegas-ry"!
而且我們自己還有賭城紀念日
"Anna-vada-versary!"
內華達紀念日！
I think we should see other people.
對，我們該開始和別人交往
We can go, right?
我們可以去吧？ 對
Great idea.
那就好 這是個好主意
I'm gonna go too!
好耶，我也要去
Phoebe,it's kind of our anniversary.
菲比，這是我倆的紀念日耶
You won't ditch me like you did with London.
少來，休想比照倫敦那次 把我甩掉
Ditch you? You were pregnant
菲比，哪有甩掉？ 當時你懷了三胞胎耶
Great story. I'm going.
真會掰，我非去不可
Listen, this weekend we're all gonna go to Las Vegas to surprise Joey!
注意，這週末大家一起去賭城 給喬伊一個驚喜
Including me!
包括我！
Do you wanna go?
你們要去嗎？
I can take a couple days off work.
我應該可以請個幾天假
Of course you can take a couple days off, because this trip includes me!
你當然可以請幾天假 因為這趟我也要去！
I've got a presentation tomorrow. I can't miss that.
等等，差點忘了 我明天要提報告，不能缺席
I've got tickets to the Van Gogh exhibit. I waited a year for this.
我也買了梵谷畫展的票 我盼了一年才盼到
Art lover.
藝術愛好者
What'd you say?
你說什麼？
I said,art lover.
我說藝術愛好者
-Was that supposed to be an insult? -I don't know,I'm very tired.
那是用來侮辱人的嗎？ 不知道，我很累了
-Rach, maybe we can fly out Saturday? -Sounds great.
瑞秋，不如你我週六再飛去？ 聽起來很可行
I'll call the airlines.
好，那我打電話去訂票
That'll be nice to have the apartment to myself.
其實想起來很不賴 我可以獨自在公寓過一晚
To walk around naked.
對，你可以脫光光到處走
No,so I can be by myself. Have a little alone time.
不是，我可以自己一個人 享受獨處的時光
Naked alone time.
脫光光的獨處時光
Just because I'm alone doesn't mean I wanna walk around naked.
菲比，我一個人獨處 並不表示我就想脫光光到處走
You live alone, you don't walk around naked.
你自己一個人住 你也不會脫光光到處走啊
Why does it takes me so long to answer the door?
你以為我為何老半天才應門？
So far,is this trip to Las Vegas better or worse than the trip to London?
這趟旅程旅程到現在為止 比起倫敦那趟好還是壞？
So far, it's pretty much the same,Phoebe.
菲比，到現在為止都差不多
What about after I give you these candies?
好，那我給你們糖果之後呢？
I guess it's a little better now.
對，我想好一點了
Las Vegas,1. London,0.
好，賭城1分，倫敦0分
I'll be back.
我馬上回來
Happy Plane-aversary.
飛機紀念日快樂
I love you.
我愛你
-Can I give you your present now? -Okay!
禮物能趁現在給你嗎？ 好啊
Oh, don't tell me I did this.
要命，不會吧？
I love "l forgot the present" fake-out!
我最愛你假裝沒帶禮物了
How about "I did forget the present, forgive me" not fake-out?
那如果我是真的沒帶禮物 請你多多包涵呢？
You can give it to me when we get back.
沒關係啦，別放在心上 等回去再給我就行了
This is the worst thing that could happen.
紀念日發生這種事 真是再掃興不過了
You decided to tell him about the Richard thing.
很好，你最後還是決定 要跟錢德說理查的事了
What "Richard thing"?
什麼理查的事？
Oh,no.
糟糕
What "Richard thing"?
什麼理查的事？
Simmons. Go with Simmons.
用西蒙斯混過去
I ran into Richard yesterday.
好吧，我昨天遇到了理查
He asked me if I wanted to go for a bite and I did.
他問我要不要一起吃飯 我答應了
I didn't tell you because you'd get mad...
我沒跟你說是因為我知道你會生氣
...and I didn't wanna spoil our anniversary.
而我不想毀了週年紀念日
I'm not mad.
我不生氣啊
Really?
真的？ 是啊…
So you bumped into Richard. You grabbed a "bite."
你遇到理查，一起吃飯
No big deal.
沒啥大不了的
Great.
太好了
Okay, London,1.
好，倫敦1分
This is gonna be a real horserace.
這將會是一場拉鋸戰
Oh,look what happened.
怎麼會這樣
Check me out.
瞧瞧我自己
I'm in my kitchen...
我在自家的廚房
...naked.
脫光光
I'm picking up an orange.
拿起一顆柳丁
I'm naked.
我脫光光
I'm lighting the candles.
點起蠟燭
Naked. And carefully.
脫光光，要小心
Oh,my God! That's Rachel, naked!
天啊，瑞秋脫光光
I can't look at that. I am looking at this.
不能看，我在看書
Okay, vivid colors, expressive brush strokes.
好，鮮明的色彩、有力的筆觸
Unless she wants me to be looking at that.
她故意要我看就另當別論了
She knows I'm home.
她知道我在家
She knows I can see her.
她知道我看得到她
What kind of game is she playing?
她這是在玩什麼把戲？
I think maybe someone's lonely tonight.
也許今晚有人寂寞
Dr. Geller.
蓋勒博士
Stop it. You're being silly.
別胡思亂想 自討沒趣了
Or am I?
真是這樣嗎？
Love to love you baby
Damn it!
討厭
May I come in?
我可以進去嗎？
Yeah,if you want to.
想要的話就進來啊
Do you want me to?
你要我進去嗎？
Yeah,sure?
當然羅？
So do l.
彼此彼此
Okay,Rach,before anything happens...
瑞秋，在一切還沒開始之前
...I wanna lay down a couple of ground rules.
有幾個原則我想先說清楚
This is just about tonight.
這只適用於今晚
I won't go through with this if it'll raise the question of "us."
今晚過後，你是你，我是我
I just want this to be...
好嗎？我希望這一切…
...about what it is.
只是各取所需
And...
...what is that,Ross?
羅斯，什麼各取所需？
The physical act of love.
出自於獸慾的性愛
What, are you crazy?
什麼？你瘋了不成？
So you weren't trying to entice me just now with your nakedness?
所以你剛才脫光光 不是在勾引我？
Oh,God. You saw me?
天啊，你有看到？
You weren't trying to entice me with your nakedness?
你脫光光不是在勾引我
You actually thought I wanted to have sex with you?
當然不是 你當真以為我想跟你上床？
才不是呢…
不是
不是…
Oh,wow. I'm sorry. But,Ross, you kicked off your shoes.
我很抱歉 可是你還把鞋踢掉了耶
-Can we just forget this ever happened? -Of course. You're right. I'm sorry.
能不能忘了這件事？ 當然可以，沒問題 你說的對，抱歉
-Thank you. -Yes.
謝謝
-I guess I'm gonna go pack. -Okay. Wait,one more thing.
那我應該回去打包了 好 等等，還有一件事
Do we still need to settle the question of "us"?
還要解決誰是誰的問題嗎？
Hey,you guys,wait! You guys.
你們等等啊
This place is much better than London.
等等我 這地方比倫敦好多了吧
A lady dressed like Cleopatra gave me this.
有個打扮成埃及艷後的女士 給了我這張折價券
Ninety-nine cent steak and lobster dinner.
99美分就能吃到牛排龍蝦晚餐
You don't eat animals.
菲比，你又不吃肉
For ninety-nine cents I'd eat you.
不用一美元，我連你都吃
I can totally settle down here.
我完全可以耗在這裡
It's got everything I could ever want. Including Joey! Look!
我要的東西應有盡有 就連喬伊都在，你們看！
Look! Hey!
快點看！
Oh,my God.
天啊
喬伊！
Love your condoms,my man.
你的保險套真不賴
Why are you here? I told you not to come.
你們怎麼在這裡？ 不是要你們別來了？
Why are you dressed as a gladiator?
你幹嘛打扮成神鬼戰士？
Because I'm shooting a scene right now. I play a gladiator.
因為我正在拍戲 我扮演神鬼戰士
Hold on a second. Can we cut?
你們等等 可以卡一下嗎？
My friends are here. I'm gonna take a break.
我朋友來了 我要休息一下
Who are you talking to?
你是在跟誰說話？
The director.
導演啊
Her.
就是她
All right,it's not a gladiator movie. I work here.
好啦，我不是在拍神鬼戰士 我在這裡工作
Why? What happened?
為什麼？發生了什麼事？
The movie shut down. Ran out of money.
那部電影因為沒錢而停拍
I'm working here till it starts up, if it ever does.
我在這裡工作等電影重新開拍 如果真有這一天的話
-I'm so sorry. -Such a drag.
我真的很遺憾
Sorry I didn't tell you. I'm sorry.
對不起 沒跟你們說，抱歉
Apparently there's a new policy of not sharing.
沒關係… 互相隱瞞顯然成了新的規矩
-I knew you weren't okay with that. -So you're a gladiator!
我就知道你聽了會有疙瘩 你是神鬼戰士耶
What's going on?
他們怎麼了？
-Monica had lunch with Richard. -Dawson?
摩妮卡跟理查吃了中飯 理查道森？（英國演員）
But that would've been so cool!
不是啦，要不然一定超酷的
Her boyfriend Richard.
是那個男朋友理查
It meant nothing. After all this time, how can you not trust me?
那根本不礙事 你怎麼到現在還不相信我？
When you go lunching with hunky men and don't tell me!
你瞞著我跟大鬍子帥哥吃午餐 要我怎麼相信你？
You're right. I'm sorry. I should've told you.
你說的對，對不起 我早該跟你說的
Thanks.
謝謝
-There we go. -Now I love Vegas.
這樣才對嘛 我愛賭城
I promise you next time I absolutely will tell you.
我保證下次一定會跟你說
-"Next time"? -So close.
下一次？ 敗在最後
There won't be a next time. You cannot see him again.
下不為例，你不能再跟他見面
I cannot see him? You can't tell me what to do.
我不能跟他見面？ 你不能對我發號施令
That's funny, I think I just did.
有趣，剛才不就是了
If you act like this, I won't be around you.
你這種態度，我眼不見為淨 我無所謂
-Fine. -Happy anniversary!
好！紀念日快樂
Guys,please! Come on,come on.
你們別這樣嘛
This is obviously a misunderstanding.
這顯然是個大誤會
No,it is not.
才不是誤會 你在說什麼…
Don't look at me. I just work here.
別看我，我只是在這裡工作
Okay, Ross? I'm a little warm, so I'm gonna be taking off my sweater.
羅斯，我有點熱，要脫毛衣
Now,I'm just letting you know...
我只是要你知道
...this is not an invitation to the physical act of love.
這不是在勾引你一夜情
Yep,that's hilarious.
對，真是太爆笑了
I'm sorry. I'm done. I'm done.
抱歉，我不鬧了…
You know,last night was embarrassing for you too.
昨晚對你其實也很尷尬
No,not really. You've seen me naked hundreds of times.
不盡然啦 你看過我裸體幾百次了
But it was a first for the rest of my building.
但對我其他樓友是第一次 好吧
That's true. But I just don't embarrass that easily.
話是這樣說沒錯啦 但我沒有那麼容易尷尬
What? You totally get embarrassed.
什麼？你根本尷尬得要死
No,I don't. Ross,I think I'm just a more secure person than you are.
才沒有 這是因為我比你更有安全感
-ls that so? -Yeah.
是嗎？ 是啊
Hey,lady!
小姐
I don't care how much you want it,okay?
不管你有多想
I am not gonna have sex with you in the bathroom!
我絕不會和你去廁所做愛
You know,in Roman times, this was more than just a hat.
在古羅馬時代 這不只是頂帽子而已
-Really? -Yeah,sure,sure.
是嗎？ 當然羅…
They would scrub the floors.
這可以用來刷地板
They'd use it to get the mud off their shoe.
抹去鞋子上的泥巴
Sometimes underneath the horse would get dirty.
有時候馬腹會弄髒
So they would stick it right
把這個戮進去就能...
I can't believe this is how I'm spending my anniversary.
喬伊，真不敢相信 我的週年紀念日是這樣過的
I'll take you someplace nice. A guy tipped me $100.
但我帶你去個好地方 今天有個人給我一百美元小費
He was playing blackjack for an hour and he won $5000.
他玩21點 才一小時就贏了五千美元
Can you believe that?
你相信嗎？五千美元耶！
If I won $5000,I'd join a gym.
若我贏了五千美元 我就去加入健身房
Build up my upper body...
把我的上半身練壯
...and hit Richard from behind with a stick.
再用棍子插理查的屁眼
Wait! Why don't I just do what that guy did?
等等，我何不傚法那個人？
I'll take this $100, turn it into $5000...
把這一百元變成五千
...and I'll turn that into enough to get my movie going!
到時再連三翻 就有錢讓電影重新開拍了
Good luck.
祝你好運了
I don't need luck. I've thought this through.
錢德，我不需要好運 我已經想透了
I see.
我懂了
Thanks.
謝謝你 多謝
I can't believe this. This is like the worst night ever.
不敢相信，今晚真是糟透了
You had a minor setback in your relationship.
摩妮卡，你和錢德的關係 有了小小挫折
Big deal. It's only Chandler.
有啥大不了？不過是錢德罷了
I am so sorry.
我真的很遺憾
This is crazy. Such a stupid argument....
我們吵架的理由太蠢了
I don't wanna see Richard.
我根本不想跟理查再見面
So go fix it.
那就去挽回啊
Find Chandler. He's probably in your room.
去找錢德 他八成就待在你房間裡
Tell him sorry and you love him.
跟他說對不起，說你愛他
You're right,Phoebe.
菲比，你說的對
-Thank you. -Sure.
謝謝你 小意思
Yeah! Las Vegas! Number one!
好耶，叫賭城第一名！
Anybody lose this?
這是誰掉的嗎？
Coming out. Place your bet.
下注吧
Dice her out.
下好離手
Yellow 11. Pay the front line!
一賠二，不還本
So I'm on my way back to the bathroom.
我正好要去廁所
All right, all right. Just keep walking, all right?
好啦…繼續走就是了
What are you? I am sorry,sir.
羅斯，你幹嘛… 先生，對不起
I think he just really likes you.
他太喜歡你了
You know that teacher who had a baby with her student?
你知道那個老師嗎？ 跟學生生孩子的那個？
搞什麼…
-Can I help you? -Yes.
嗨 小姐，需要我效勞嗎？對
Do you have any extra pants? My friend seems to have had a little accident.
不好意思 你們有多的褲子嗎？ 我朋友出了點小狀況
-Can I change $100? -Changing $100.
可以換一百元籌碼嗎？ 換一百元籌碼
-Good luck, sir. -Thanks.
先生，祝您好運
That's right.
全押了
-Thirteen. -Hit me!
13點 再來
Oh,man!
要命！
Wait!
慢著！
You are not gonna believe this!
錢德，說了你一定不相信
I have found my identical hand twin.
我找到我的雙胞手了！
What?
什麼？
My identical hand twin!
我的雙胞手啊！
What's an identical hand twin?
什麼是雙胞手？
What does it sound like?
聽起來像什麼？
It's a guy with my identical hands.
有個人的手跟我一模一樣
It was incredible. The dealer's hands were exactly like mine.
錢德，太不可思議了 發牌員的手跟我一模一樣
It was like looking at my hands in a mirror!
就跟照鏡子沒兩樣
You sure you weren't looking at your hands in a mirror?
你確定不是在照鏡子？
Don't you see what this means? I can forget about that stupid movie.
你不懂這件事的意義嗎？ 我大可忘了那部蠢電影
I'm gonna be a millionaire!
我要變成百萬富翁了！
-How? -I don't have it all worked out yet.
怎麼變？ 我還沒有完全想出來
But it's gotta mean big money. Come on, identical hands!
不過保證很有賺頭 拜託，一模一樣的手耶！
Again,I must go back to...
我得再問一次
...how?
怎麼賺？
This is Vegas,man. People will pay to see freaky stuff!
這裡可是賭城 大家就愛付錢看怪東西
How much would you pay to see this hand...
好，你願意付多少錢 看這隻手
...twice?
兩次？
I can't really put a price on that.
喬伊，我說不太出個價錢
Are you un-supporting me again?
你又不支持我了？
I support you 100%. I just didn't get it right away.
不…我百分之百支持你 只是我一時沒回過神來
Now I'm caught up.
我現在懂了
Identical hand twins.
雙胞手！
It's a million-dollar idea!
這點子值上一百萬
Right? I know. Okay. All right.
我知道…
What's that for?
那是幹嘛的？
Well,I gotta document this before that dealer gets off his break.
照相存證，免得發牌員落跑
I found my identical hand twin!
我找到我的雙胞手了！
Oh,you're so lucky!
你真幸運
So where's Monica? Did you guys make up?
摩妮卡呢？你們和好沒？
But she just came up here.
沒有啊 可是她剛才上來了啊
That was Joey.
那是喬伊
I wonder where she is? It's so weird.
怪了，那她去了哪裡？
She's probably talking to Richard.
或許在跟理查說話吧
Would you stop that?
你有完沒完？
You know what she said after her lunch with Richard?
你知道他和理查吃完中飯 回來後第一句話是什麼嗎？
She didn't feel anything for him. She loves you.
她對他完全沒感覺了 她愛的是你
-Really? -Yes.
真的？ 對
She feels terrible. She really wants to make up. You've gotta find her.
而且她很難過 她真的很想跟你和好 你一定得找到她
Good.
好
I should really start wearing hats.
我真應該開始戴帽子
我的色子呢？
Welcome to Las Vegas.
歡迎來到賭城
-Did you enjoy your flight? -I did.
一路還愉快嗎？ 對
Thank you very much. It was excellent.
謝謝，非常棒
-I hope you had a nice flight. -Oh,it was the best.
希望您一路還愉快 太愉快了
I think the check-in is that way.
登記櫃檯應該在那裡
Kids love me.
小孩子最喜歡我了
Hi,you guys are here!
菲比 你們來了！
What'd you do? Did you go to a costume party?
嗨 你去參加化妝舞會了？
Let me guess. Pancho Villa.
我來猜，你是扮龐丘維亞（墨西哥革命英雄）？
And you're Bob Saget.
你是鮑伯塞吉（演員）
Pancho Villa?
龐丘維亞？ 是啊
What are you talking about,Phoebe? I don't
菲比，你在說什麼啊？ 我不…
Oh,my God! You drew on me?
天啊，你偷畫我？
Hey,you wet my pants!
誰叫你弄濕我褲子！
What kind of party was this?
這是哪種派對啊？
I've been walking around like this? You have so crossed a line.
我打從下飛機就是這樣子 你實在是太過份了
Rach,wait. The men's room is that way.
瑞秋，等等，男廁在那裡
It's the third time she's won on a machine I was playing.
怎麼了？ 那女士接我手玩，結果贏錢 這已經是第三次了
I bet she's one of those people.
我賭她一定是那種人
Mole people?
間諜？
What? No, a lurker.
不是啦，是跟賭人
What's that?
跟賭人是什麼？
When you're playing a machine and it hasn't paid out...
你玩賭博機，沒有贏錢
...a lurker waits for you to give up and then
跟賭人等你放棄就來接手玩 然後…
Kills you?
殺你滅口？
They swoop in and steal your jackpot.
不是啦，他們半路殺進來 偷走本來你會中的大獎
-How do you know about this? -My nana used to do it.
你怎麼會知道這種事 我褓姆以前就幹這行
That's how she paid for my dance Karate lessons.
她就是用這收入 幫我付舞蹈…空手道的學費
Dance karate?
舞蹈空手道？
Yes,it's a deadly...
對，那是種...
...but beautiful sport.
...美麗卻致命的運動
-lt won't come off. -What?
我弄不掉 什麼？
It won't come off.
我弄不掉
Oh,my God. Rach, are you sure?
天啊，瑞秋，你確定嗎？
I took it off and then I drew it back on.
不確定，其實我弄掉了 又自己再畫回去
Rach,I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I'm sure we can get it off,okay?
我真的很抱歉 我確定一定可以弄掉的
-Just give me your pen. -Why? What are you gonna do?
把你的筆給我 幹嘛？做什麼用？
Well,I believe I'm going to stab you repeatedly.
我要讓你萬筆穿心
Not here. There are cameras everywhere.
別在這裡 到處都有監視攝影機
You made it!
你們到了！
喬伊
Who's your friend? He's hot.
你朋友是誰？他真辣
Thanks,man.
多謝誇獎
Listen,I talked to Chandler. And I'm sorry about the movie.
錢德跟我說過了 電影的事我很遺憾
Don't be sorry.
不用抱歉
I don't need it anymore. I found my identical hand twin.
不要也罷 我找到我的雙胞手
Your what?
你的什麼？
My identical hand twin. The person whose hands are like mine.
我的雙胞手 那個人的手掌跟我完全一樣
-Were you looking for this person? -Not even. This thing is a gold mine.
你特別去找的？ 正好撞見的，這可是金礦
What?
什麼？
That won't make you any money.
靠那個賺不了錢的
Well,fine.
好，你這樣想也無所謂
None of you will live with me in my hand-shaped mansion.
到時我蓋了手掌形的大廈 你們誰都休想來住
Except you. You can live in the thumb.
菲比，你例外，大拇指給你住
All right,baby,come on!
好吧，加油！
I am on fire!
漂亮！擋都擋不住！
See you later.
摩妮卡，再見
What are you doing?
等等，錢德，你在幹嘛？
What's it look like? Going home.
你看呢？我要回家
Why?
等等，為什麼？
Wait. Sorry,I was just playing for one second.
你等等 對不起，我只是下來玩一下
If you don't want me to see Richard again,I won't.
我本來打算要跟你說 若你不讓我理查再見面 我答應
He means nothing to me.
他對我沒有任何意義
Oh,come on. I was there.
得了吧，我又不是瞎子
I know he's the love of your life.
我知道他是你追求的真愛
Not anymore.
現在不是了
Really?
真的？
Really.
真的
All right?
Let's forget about going home and celebrate our anniversary.
忘了什麼要回家的事 我們來慶祝週年紀念日
Okay, this is empty.
袋子裡是空的
I wanted to make a dramatic scene, but I hate packing.
我想要搞得很戲劇化 可是我又討厭打包
Where's the other guy?
另一個人呢？
Which guy?
哪個人？
Tall,dark hair,hand looks exactly like this?
高高的，深色頭髮 手掌跟我一模一樣，你看
I don't know about the hands, but he went to the restroom.
我不知道什麼手掌的 不過在我之前的發牌員 剛去上廁所了
好
How you doing?
你好嗎？
-Very busy. -Right. Okay.
我很忙 對耶！好吧
Yes,hello. I have a question.
你好，我有個問題
I used your pen to draw on my friend's face.
我用你們的筆，畫我朋友的臉
A beard and a mustache.
畫了鬍子
Thank you.
謝謝你
No,she didn't think so.
不，她不以為然
I know. It's like Anyway....
對啊，那其實…
Makeup didn't cover it, we've tried everything and nothing's worked.
用化妝品蓋不過去 我們試過所有方法都去不掉
What do we do?
這要怎麼辦？
對，是…
Thank you.
好…多謝
Yeah, it's not coming off.
對，這個墨水擦不掉
What? What else did he say?
什麼？那他還說了什麼？
He said he thought I was funny.
他說他覺得我很逗
Okay, look. Let's just go downstairs...
好，你聽我說… 我們下樓去...
...we'll have some fun and you will forget all about it.
好好玩玩 你就會忘記這回事了
There's no way I am leaving looking like this!
休想，羅斯，我頂著這個樣子 絕對不出房門
Come on,Rach. It's not that bad.
別這樣啦，沒有那麼難看
Ross,I am a human doodle!
羅斯，我變成人體塗鴉了！
Just because some idiot drew on your face doesn't mean you can't have fun.
別因為一個白癡在你臉上亂畫 而阻礙你玩樂的權利
Besides,no one will even look at you.
而且又沒人會看你
This is Vegas. Hello? There are tons of other freaks here.
這裡可是賭城，怪人一大堆
There are tons of freaks here. No other. No.
這裡有一大堆怪人，你不算
Come on. No one will notice. I swear.
走啦，我發誓沒人會注意到
There was some staring and pointing.
好啦，是有一些人指指點點
I need a drink.
我得喝點酒
They really overcharge you for that stuff.
冰箱裡的酒都太貴了
But who cares, because it's all on me.
但是誰在乎呢？我請客
That is one big drink.
你的一點酒還真不少
Macadamia nut?
要吃夏威夷果仁嗎？
Wow! That's some pricey nut.
這個果仁還真值錢
Really like those macadamia nuts?
你真的很喜歡吃果仁呢
Nope.
不喜歡
Get out of here, you lurker!
跟賭人，走開啦
Go on,get!
滾啦
You made up.
你們和好了
I couldn't be mad at him for too long.
是啊，我沒辦法一直生他的氣
She couldn't live without the "Chand love."
沒有錢德的愛，她就不能活
Get a room.
去開房間啦
-We have one. -Use it.
我們有房間 我知道，快去用啊
Bye,Chandler. Bye,Mon.
錢德，摩妮卡，再見
Phoebe,Phoebe. Please pick up a house phone.
菲比…請至店內接電話
You have a call from Chandler and Mon.
錢德和摩妮卡有事找
Hello,Chandler and Mon. Hello?
喂？錢德、摩妮卡，喂？…
You dirty lurker!
你這個死跟賭人
I'm sorry,you are the same old lady,right? Yeah. Dirty lurker!
抱歉，你就是那位老太太吧？ 死跟賭人！
That's right. Take good care of those babies.
可得好好照顧你的手
Excuse me?
你說什麼？
It's me. Joey.
我是喬伊啊
Do I know you?
我認識你嗎？
Joey?
喬伊啊
Yeah, the hand guy.
秀手的那個
So, what are we gonna do about this hand twin thing?
我們要怎麼處理雙胞手的事？
Nothing.
不用處理？
Look,you and I have been given a gift.
你和我擁有上帝的賜禮
We have to do something with it. Like hand modeling. Or magic.
我們得要好好利用 好比手部模特兒或是變魔術
And you know NASA's gonna want to talk to us.
太空總署一定也想找我們聊聊
I have to get back to work.
我得回去工作了… 等等…
We can have our own show.
我們可以自己組秀
We can clap our hands together. People will love it!
我們把手掌合在一起 大家一定超愛看的
And I wrote a song for us.
我還替我們寫了一首主題曲
This hand is your hand
這是你的手
This hand is my hand
這是我的手
Oh,wait,that's your hand
等等，那是你的手才對
No,wait,it's my hand
不對，是我的手才對
-That's okay. -But you haven't even heard the chorus!
還是算了 你還沒聽到副歌啊
Oh,my God.
天啊
I look like my great-aunt Muriel.
我現在看起來 就像我姑婆茉莉兒
All right,you know what?
We don't have to go downstairs.
其實我們用不著下樓
We can bring Vegas up to us.
房間裡就可以是賭城
All right,come on.
快
We'll play some blackjack. Here we go.
我們來玩21點 來羅
-Thirteen. -Hit me.
13點 再加
Twenty-three.
23，爆了
Which is what we play to at this casino!
我們這裡23點最大
You win 10 dollars!
你贏了10美元
-I bet 20. -Right.
我押了20美元 沒錯
A new pair of shoes for the Chan-Chan man!
幫我的小錢錢買雙新鞋
I've never seen a roll like this!
我這輩子還沒看過有這麼旺的
That's right, baby!
寶貝，你說對了
What do I want now?
這次要押幾號？
Eight?
好，8號？
-Six. -Pick a number! That is your only job.
還是6號？ 選一個啦！你只有這個任務！
-Eight. -Thank you.
8號… 8號
If you get this, we buy everybody a steak dinner.
如果你中了這一把 晚餐就請在場的各位吃牛排
Eight it is.
8號
We're not buying steak dinners,are we?
我們真的要請他們吃牛排？
-No. -Okay,good.
假的 那就好
-What do I want now? -Try a hard eight.
這次要押幾號？ 再硬押個8
-What? -Two fours.
什麼？4加4啦
Eight!
8號
Don't you let her go. You're a lucky guy.
千萬要把握住她，你太幸運了
Thank you,Mr. Drunken Gambler.
謝謝你，醉賭徒先生
You get this and we get the biggest suite in the place.
好，如果你中了這一把 我們就租下這裡最大的套房
We get the biggest suite in the place.
等等…我說的是我和她租下這裡最大的套房
The biggest suite in the place!
好，這裡最大的套房來羅
Come on!
I love you! I can't remember why we fought.
我愛你 我都忘記我們在吵什麼了
Because I had lunch with Rich
因為我和理查吃中飯…
Me neither!
我也忘了！
-What now? -Another hard eight.
這次要押幾號？ 再硬押一次8
Hard eight? Let's call it easy eight!
硬押8？簡單8才對
I'll tell you what. You roll another hard eight...
好，這樣吧，如果這次再中…
...and we get married here tonight.
我們今晚就在這裡結婚
快啊…
Shut up!
閉嘴！
It just got interesting!
好戲才正要上場！
What did you say?
你剛才說什麼？
You roll another hard eight, we get married tonight.
你再贏一次8 我們今晚就在這裡結婚
You serious?
你是認真的？
Yes. I love you.
是啊，我愛你
I've never loved anybody as much as I love you.
我不曾這樣愛過一個人
我也不曾這樣愛過一個人
So if an eight comes up, we take it as a sign and we do it.
好，如果再出8就是天意 我們趕今晚結婚
What do you say?
好不好？
Okay.
好
來吧…
That's a four.
有一個是4
-And where's the other one? -Under the table.
另一個呢？ 掉到桌子底下了
Nobody move! You look that way,I look this way.
通通不許動！ 你找那邊，我找這邊 好！
Here it is,here it is.
在這裡…
That could be 4 or 5.
一半4，一半5
It's your call.
你決定
It's a four.
那是4
I think so too.
我也這樣覺得
Oh, well, lost again.
好吧，又沒贏到錢
That's it. You and me. Outside!
夠了，我們去外面解決
I wouldn't want you to lose a chunk of that pretty blond hair!
我可不想看到 你美麗的金髮少了一撮
Be cool.
假裝沒事…
Okay, your lurking days are over.
女士，你跟賭的日子結束了
What?
什麼？
Everyone you lurk, I'll lurk first.
從現在開始 我要搶先你一步
You move on, I'll be one step ahead of you...
不管你找誰下手 我都會捷足先登
...every single time.
一次都不放過
And then I'll be on your ass every hour of every day...
我每天都會緊緊跟著你…
...till Monday...
直到星期一
...because that's when I go home.
因為我那天要回家
When do you leave?
你何時要回家？
Also Monday.
也是星期一
What time? Maybe we can share a cab.
幾點？說不定能共乘計程車
Hit me.
再加
We need more cards.
我們得再去買牌
Yeah. And we also need more drinks. Hold on a second.
對，還要再來點酒，你等等
好了
Hello,Vegas?
賭城嗎？
We would like more alcohol.
我們還需要酒
You know what else? We would like some more beers.
對了，再來點啤酒
Oh,I forgot to dial.
我竟然忘了撥號
That must be our alcohol and beers.
一定是送酒來了
It's Joey! I love Joey!
是喬伊！我愛喬伊
Oh,I love Joey!
我愛喬伊
Joey lives with a duck.
喬伊跟鴨子住一起
嗨
Look,I need some help, okay?
你們聽我說，我需要幫助
Someone has to convince my hand twin to cooperate.
誰去叫我那雙胞手合作點
I'll do it. Whatever you need me to do, I'm your man.
我去 不管你有什麼需要 找我就對了
Are you okay?
你還好吧？
Yeah. Fine. Thanks.
對，我很好，謝了
Hey, Rach?
瑞秋
How you doing?
你好嗎？
I'm doing good, baby. How you doing?
寶貝，我很好，你呢？
Don't let her drink anymore.
羅斯，別再讓她喝了
Here's that macadamia nut.
是那顆夏威夷果仁
No,something else.
不對，是別的東西
So, what do you wanna do now?
好吧，你現在要幹嘛？
I wanna get out of the room.
我要離開這房間
I really miss downstairs.
我真想念樓下
Okay,you know what? There is only one way I am leaving this hotel room.
我跟你說，要我離開這間房 只有一個方法
Well,hello!
嗨
I'm Ross.
我是羅斯
-Good luck to you. -Sir, you've got a little something....
祝你好運 抱歉，先生，你臉上有東西
Hello.
你好 你好
你好
I won!
我贏了！
I won! I finally won!
我贏了！我終於贏了
I won! That was my quarter!
是我贏才對，那是我的硬幣
Take a hike, toots.
好啦，還給你，滾吧
Excuse me, sir.
先生，不好意思
This lady played my quarter. This is my money.
這位小姐用我的硬幣玩 這是我贏的錢
Is that true, miss?
小姐，真的是這樣嗎？
Sells drugs to kids.
賣毒品給小孩
什麼？
She sells drugs to kids.
她賣毒品給小孩
It was my quarter.
那是我的硬幣
Was it her quarter?
那硬幣是她的嗎？
How about we talk about this over dinner?
我們等吃晚餐再聊如何？
-Okay, lady, you're out of here. -No,you can't arrest me!
好了，小姐，請你出去 不！…你不能逮捕我
I won't go back to that hellhole!
我才不要重回火坑！
I'm just taking you outside.
我只是要把你帶出去而已
那好吧
I need something old, something new, something borrowed and something blue.
快點，一定要湊齊四樣東西 我們才能結婚
Here's something blue and new.
這是藍色的，而且也是新的
You are so efficient. I love you.
我們真有效率，我愛你
-Let's go. -No,wait!
走吧 還不行…
We need something old.
我們還需要舊的東西
I have a condom in my wallet that I've had since I was twelve.
好，我皮夾裡有個保險套 我從12歲放到現在
That'll work.
那符合啊（亦指「還能用」）
I don't think so.
我想應該不能用了
Now something borrowed.
好，現在只剩借來的東西
Here, just take this.
那就把這毛衣拿走
That's stealing.
這是偷竊耶
We'll bring it back. Put it under your dress.
到時再還回來就是了 塞進你的洋裝裡
Okay. One thing at a time.
好啦，先結婚再懷孕
-Are you gonna play? -No,I don't really have any money.
你要玩嗎？ 不要，我沒半毛錢
Not yet,anyway.
只是時候未到而已
Can't sit here if you don't play.
你不玩就不能坐在這裡
My name is Regina Falangie.
嗨，我是瑞吉娜佛蘭姬
I'm a businesswoman in town on business.
我是生意人，這趟是來出差的
Would you like to see my card?
你要我的名片嗎？
What did I do with my Filofax?
我的名片夾到哪兒去了？
I must've left it in Conference Room B.
一定是忘在B會議室
-Fourteen. -Hit me.
14點 再加
Oh,my God.
天啊
May I just say that you two gentlemen have the exact same hands?
兩位的手一模一樣
They're identical.
一個模子刻出來的
I've never seen that in the business world.
我在商業界做了這麼久 從來沒看過這種事
Stop it.
別再說了
Miss Falangie,may I ask you a question as an impartial person at this table?
佛蘭姬女士，以局外人的身份 我能請教你一個問題嗎？
Please stop it.
請你別再說了
Wouldn't you pay good money to see identical hands...
你願不願意花大錢 去看手長一模一樣的兩個人…
...showcased in some type of an entertainment venue?
這種娛樂性的演出？
If you leave now,I will chop off my hand and give it to you!
只要你願意離開 我就把手砍下來送你！
Didn't I just throw you out?
我不是才把你趕出去了嗎？
No, you threw out Phoebe.
不，你趕出去的是菲比
I'm Regina Falangie. Falangie.
我是瑞吉娜佛蘭姬女士
Come on, lady.
小姐，你別鬧了
Please take him too.
請你把他也帶走
Me? Oh, come on, man.
我？別這樣嘛
Come on, buddy.
走吧…
Don't let him do this. Come on!
你不能這樣
I'm your hand twin!
我是你的雙胞手耶
Hello. One marriage,please.
嗨，登記結婚
We want to get married.
對，我們要結婚
There's a service in progress. Have a seat.
有婚禮正在進行，先請坐
All right.
好吧…
What are you doing?
你在幹嘛？
The "Wedding March." Does that freak you out?
那是結婚進行曲 聽了有沒有嚇到？
No, it's the graduation song.
沒有，因為那是畢業歌
This is it. We're gonna get married.
好，來吧 我們要結婚了
You sure you wanna do this?
你確定你真的想結婚？
Hello, Mrs. Ross!
嗨，羅斯太太
Well,hello, Mr. Rachel!
嗨，瑞秋先生
Wait. Okay.
等等，好